<div>
<pre style="font-style:Courier New, courier, serif;font-size: 12px">

<h1>Some admin tips and how-tos</h1>
<h2>How to change the look of the site</h2>
There are several ways to change the look of the site depending on how much 
you want to change.

<b>To Change The Titles/Footers and Other Stuff</b>

Select '<b>Template Tags</b>' from 'Configure Site' menu on the left. There you
can change the title, footer, copyright notice etc. that will be included 
in every page on the site. The big boxes take HTML markup, the smaller ones
just text. (For very advanced users and template writers you can create
your own tags and fill them out here too. More on that later.)

<b>To Change The Menus</b>

Use the <b>Menus</b> and <b>Menu Groups</b> items from the 'Configure Site' 
menu on the left to change which menu items show up for what kind of user
and in which group, as well as the order of items and groups.

<b>Changing Elements on the Page</b>

A few of the elements on the page can selected on/off. Select '<b>Page
Content</b>' from the Configure Site menu to choose what is on each
page. 

[note: this list is small but we expect people to contribute more
elements -- read on to see how this is done...]


<b>To Change Styles (layout, colors, fonts, etc.)</b>

Currently there is no interactive way to change styles on the site. 
However, the site was designed so that <b>ALL</b> formatting is handled 
by a single file so if you know some CSS you can create an entire 
look and feel (a.k.a. skin) for the site by simply editing a single 
CSS file. 

You can see this in action by selecting the '<b>Settings</b>' option on
the left and select a different style sheet. All of these 'skins' are
done by only editing a single CSS file. (Clever use of background
images obviates the need to edit any HTML.)

To create your own CSS/skin you can either start by copying one of
the existing .css files or you can start from scratch using <i>skin-blank.css</i>
(make sure to make a copy of blank so you always have one around).

Name your CSS/skin with the prefix 'skin-' (e.g. 'skin-myskin.css').
Place your CSS/skin file in the templates directory it will
be seen by the 'Settings' form. There you can select it as the default
skin for the site.

<b>Adding Custom HTML Elements</b>

Sometimes you may find that you want new HTML elements that simply can't
be duplicated in CSS or you have additional functionality you want to
express in HTML.

You can add individual elements into the templates/custom.xml file. This
file is in TAL format which, even if aren't familiar with, is pretty easy
to understand by looking at the examples in the shipping version of that
file. 

Every 'metal macro' defined in that file is automatically detected by
the system and can be turned on/off by selecting '<b>Page Content</b>' 
from the menu on the left. (The default is 'off' so once you edit
custom.xml you have to turn it 'on' before it will appear on the page.)

[note: some of the custom macros make 'calls' back into the PHP code
using a special API -- this is API is highly experimental and pretty
much undefined. If you really know what you're doing you can actually
add an include file to <i>cc-includes.php</i> and all those functions
will be 'visible' to macros in custom.xml so you can dynamically
populate your custom HTML element. Fun, flexible and dangerous.]

<b>To Really Hork the Site's HTML</b>

The site was designed so that <b>ALL</b> visual elements are constructed
using TAL templates. <i>Absolutely no user interface is in the PHP code</i>
with the exception of some form elements (e.g. edit fields, radio buttons,
etc.)

<b>ALL</b> of the user interface is controlled by these two files:

- cctemplates/template-page.html
- cctemplates/macros.xml

You will note there is abolsutely no style information in these files.
You would be well advised to keep that way so that other skins might
continue to work even if you have changed structural layout.

These are dense files and not for the faint of heart but if you really
want to completely rearrange the site's layout and you're sure you
can't get what you want from changing the CSS.


</pre>
</div>