<div>
<pre style="font-style:Courier New, courier, serif;font-size: 12px">

<h1>How to Create a Virtual Installation</h1>

Your CC Host site can be configured to look like many different
sites with just a few menu selections (and no changes to your 
web server).

Why do this? Let's say you are running a remix community as
your main site but also want to run a contest (or you
mainly run contests and you also want to have a personal
'media weblog' on the side -- or -- whatever).

In this case you want to have a 'virtual face' to the site
without the hassle of reinstalling or major configuation
hoops.

<h2>Creating a Virtual Personal Media Weblog</h2>

[note: 'pretty urls' are currently off in the alpha so the
following includes all this '?mode=/' gobbledy gook in the
URLs, that will go away when pretty urls are working again.]

As an example let's say you wanted a virtual site that was your 
own person media weblog for remixes.

1) Pick a name for the new virtual face (e.g. 'myremixes')
and type into your browser like this:

   ${root-url}?mode=/myremixes

2) There is no step 2.

In order to customize this virtual installation select '<b>Setting</b>'
and pick another skin, or select <b>Menus</b> to change the menus.

All the configuration settings you make (except for a few things
like 'Global Setup' and 'Database') will only be applied to your
new virtual site. Use the url above as your 'home' url and you're 
on your way.

For the personal remix weblog you will probably want to restrict
the menus so that only you (as admin) have the ability to upload
or register so in the menu configuation you mark everything you
don't want anybody to see as 'Admin only'.

<h2>Creating a Virtual Contest Site</h2>

If you run regular contests you can set up a virtual site for
every contest, each with it's own skin (look and feel) and
functionality (what file formats are allowed, etc.)

Here's a way to do it:

1) Create the contest and note the 'internal name' you give it
(e.g. 'myfirstcontest')

2) Now create the virtual site by browsing to:

   ${root-url}?mode=/myfirstcontest

3) Select '<b>Settings</b>' from the menu.

4) In the 'Homepage' field type the following:

    <b>contest/myfirstcontest</b>

5) Select your skin from the drop down.

Now edit the menus to cut them down to just what you
want people to see.

<h2>Other Virtual Sites</h2>

The two cases above are what we came up with. You may
have a whole other set of cases. 

For example, in a community setting you may chose to give 
each member (or selected members) the ability to customize 
their own pages. As administrator you can setup a virtual 
site for each person assigning their member's page as the 
home page for that virtual site and even allow them to 
submit a CSS skin just for their version of the site.

Because you edit the menus you can control what that user
or other members see when they are looking at that virtual
site. 

And whatever else you can think of.

</pre>
</div>